Innocence isn't lost. It's taken.
Cracks is a drama, mystery, thriller film directed by Jordan Scott.
Jealousy flares after the headmistress of an elite boarding
school for girls becomes obsessed with a new student.
Miss G, played by Eva Green.
Di, played by Juno Temple.
Fiamma, played by María Valverde.
Poppy, played by Imogen Poots.
Lily, played by Ellie Nunn.
Laurel, played by Adele McCann.
Cracks is a 2009 independent drama film directed by Jordan Scott, starring
Eva Green, Juno Temple, María Valverde and Imogen Poots.
It was released theatrically in the United Kingdom
and Ireland on 4 December 2009.
In the United States, it was released by IFC Films theatrically on 18 March 2011 and premiered on television
on Showtime as part of an ongoing pay television broadcast deal with IFC later in the year.
The film was produced in May 2008, written for the screen by Caroline Ip, Ben Court
and Jordan Scott, based on the 1999 novel written by Sheila Kohler.
Kwesi Dickson, Andrew Lowe, Julie Payne, Rosalie Swedlin
and Christine Vachon were the producers.
Ridley and Tony Scott served as executive producers.
The film was mostly filmed in County Wicklow, Ireland.
The film explores themes of uniform, based on novel
or book, nightmare, england, teacher.
The tone is intense and emotional and mind_bending.